General Still Photograph Collection
General Still Photograph Collection
- Photographs
  - Gobel, George - NBC, George Gobel Show (shown with Eddie Fisher), 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Gobel, George - NBC, Lux Show, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Goodman, Benny - CBS, Music U.S.A., 8/26/58 (Box 1)
  - Gorin, Igor - NBC, Rigoletto, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Gorme, Eydie - NBC, Steve Allen Show, 1/17/58 (Box 2)
  - Gorme, Eydie - NBC, Steve Allen Presents Steve Lawrence and Eydie Gorme, 6/20/58 (Box 1)
  - Gorme, Eydie - NBC, Steve Allen Presents Steve Lawrence and Eydie Gorme, 8/8/58 (Box 1)
  - Gosfield, Maurice - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Bilko's Prize Poodle (shown with poodle, Louise), 5/20/58 (Box 1)
  - Goulding, Ray - NBC, Monitor (radio broadcast), 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Grable, Betty - CBS, Lucille Ball-Desi Arnaz Show, 1/21/58 (Box 2)
  - Granger, Farley - CBS, United States Steel Hour: Hidden River, 6/19/58 (Box 1)
  - Grant, Lee - NBC, Three Plays by Tennessee Williams (Box 1)
  - Grauer, Bennett - NBC, Monitor (radio broadcast), 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Gray, Donald - NBC, Saber of London (shown with another man), 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Gray, Vernon - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Sleeping Beauty, 5/16/58 (Box 1)
  - Gray, Vernon - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Sleeping Beauty, 5/16/58 (Box 1)
  - Greenberg, Ronnie - NBC, Dough Re Mi (Box 1)
  - Grey, Virginia - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Easy-Going Man, 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Grey, Virginia - NBC, Wagon Train: Honorable Don Charlie, 1/3/58 (Box 2)
  - Griffin, Merv - CBS, Play Your Hunch, 6/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Griffin, Merv - CBS, Play Your Hunch (shown with Bill Nimmo), 7/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Grunfeld, Svea - NBC, A Night to Remember (with child actress) (Box 1)
  - Guardino, Harry - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: Mother Bit, 5/31/57 (Box 2)
  - Hale, Barbara - CBS, Perry Mason: Case of the Corresponding Corpse, 8/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Hall, Monty - CBS, Keep Talking, 6/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Halpern, Luke - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: Matter of Guilt, A, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - Halpin, Luke - CBS, Beaver Patrol, 3/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Harman, Joy - NBC, Steve Allen Show, 7/12/57 (Box 2)
  - Harris, Rosemary - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: A Tale of Two Cities, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Harris, Rosemary - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: A Tale of Two Cities, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Harris, Rosemary - NBC, Hallmark Hall of Fame: Dial 'M' for Murder, 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Hart, Freddie - NBC, Life of Riley: Otis Yonder Story (Box 1)
  - Hatfield, Hurd - CBS, Climax!: Cabin B-13 (Box 1)
  - Hayakawa, Sessue - CBS, Red Skelton Show, 6/5/58 (Box 1)
  - Hayes, Bill - CBS, United States Steel Hour: Family Alliance, A, 5/21/58 (Box 1)
  - Hayes, Helen - CBS, Playhouse 90: Four Women in Black, 7/23/57 (Box 2)
  - Hayes, Rita - NBC, Win With a Winner (shown with 7 other women), 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Hayward, Louis - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Contest of Ladies, A, 3/26/58 (Box 1)
  - Heinkel, Susan - CBS, Susan's Show, 7/9/57 (Box 2)
  - Heintz, Lee - NBC, Ford Show, 5/31/57 (Box 2)
  - Helm, Anne - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Sleeping Beauty, 5/16/58 (Box 1)
  - Helm, Anne - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Sleeping Beauty, 5/16/58 (Box 1)
  - Helmore, Tom - CBS, No Second Helping, 6/13/58 (Box 1)
  - Henderson, Florence - CBS, United States Steel Hour: Family Alliance, A, 5/21/58 (Box 1)
  - Henderson, Skitch - NBC, NBC Bandstand (radio broadcast), 6/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Hengen, Dabby - NBC, Wagon Train: Sarah Drummond Story, 3/7/58 (Box 1)
  - Henreid, Paul - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Hands of the Enemy, 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Henrich, Tommy - NBC, Big Moment, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Herbert, Don - NBC, Watch Mr. Wizard, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Hickey, William - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: Love Me to Pieces, 7/8/57 (Box 2)
  - Hitchcock, Patricia - NBC, Life of Riley: Movie Struck, 1/3/58 (Box 2)
  - Hogan, Ben - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show, 3/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Homeier, Skip - CBS, Millionaire: Story of Wally Bannister, 4/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Hong, James - CBS, Playhouse 90: Nightmare at Ground Zero, 5/2/58 (Box 1)
  - Hope, Bob - NBC, Bob Hope Buick Show: Roberta, 8/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Hope, Bob - NBC, Bob Hope Buick Show: Roberta, 8/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Horton, Robert - NBC, Wagon Train, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Horton, Robert - NBC, Wagon Train: Sarah Drummond Story, 3/7/58 (Box 1)
  - Hull, Scodina - NBC, Haggis Baggis (shown with 7 other women), 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Humamura, Michiko - CBS, Big Record, 8/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Hunter, Tab - NBC, Hallmark Hail of Fame: Hans Brinker or The Silver Skates, 1/10/58 (Box 2)
  - Hunter, Tab - CBS, Playhouse 90: Portrait of a Murderer, 8/5/58 (Box 1)
  - Huntley, Chet - NBC, NBC News: Outlook, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Huntley, Chet - NBC, NBC News: Outlook (shown with Israeli teenagers), 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Huntley, Chet - NBC, NBC News: Huntley-Brinkley Report, 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Jackson, Jay - NBC, Tic Tac Dough (shown with 7 other hosts), 7/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Jackson, Tommy "Hurricane" - NBC, Heavyweight Championship Fight, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - Jaeckel, Richard - CBS, Millionaire, 8/13/58 (Box 1)
  - Jameson, Joyce - NBC, Steve Allen Show (shown 4 times in different character), 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Jameson, Joyce - NBC, Club Oasis Starring Spike Jones, 6/13/58 (Box 1)
  - Jameson, Joyce - NBC (comedienne posing for Jack Zwillinger), 6/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Jameson, Joyce - NBC, Steve Allen Show (Box 1)
  - Janssen, David - CBS, Richard Diamond, Private Detective, 6/24/57 (Box 2)
  - Janssen, David - CBS, Richard Diamond, Private Detective, 3/20/58 (Box 1)
  - Jeffreys, Anne - ABC, Love That Jill: They Went Thataway (Box 2)
  - Johns, Glynis - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Dead Are Silent, 7/19/57 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Betty - NBC, Jack Paar Show, 5/9/58 (Box 1)
  - Johnson, Georgann - CBS, Millionaire: Story of Jerry Bell, 7/29/57 (Box 1)
  - Jone, Barry - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Magic Fishbone, 8/1/58 (Box 1)
  - Jones, Barry - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Magic Fishbone (with family sitting around a table) (Box 1)
  - Jones, Carolyn - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Girl in the Grass, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - Jones, Gordon - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Magic of Three (Box 1)
  - Jones, Gordon - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Safe (Box 2)
  - Jones, Shirley - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Red Mill, 4/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Jones, Shirley - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Red Mill, 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Jones, Spike - NBC, Club Oasis Starring Spike Jones, 6/13/58 (Box 1)
  - Joslyn, Allyn - CBS, Eve Arden Show, 8/22/57 (Box 1)
  - Kallir, Lilian - NBC, Telephone Hour (radio broadcast), 4/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Karloff, Boris (Kate Smith's Birthday Party), 6/10/57 (Box 2)
  - Kasznar, Kurt - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Rumpelstiltskin, 1/17/58 (Box 2)
  - Kaye, Stubby - NBC, Hansel and Gretel (also on radio), 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Keane, Teri - NBC, Don Ameche's Real Life Stories, 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Keel, Howard - NBC, Bob Hope Buick Show: Roberta, 8/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Kell, George - CBS, George Kell at Game of the Week, 4/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Kelly, Gene - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Life You Save, 9/6/57 (Box 2)
  - Kennedy, Tom - NBC, Big Game, 6/13/58 (Box 1)
  - Kennedy, Adam - NBC, Californians (shown with 2 others), 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Kennedy, Bob - CBS, Wingo, 3/27/58 (Box 1)
  - Keymas, George - CBS, Playhouse 90: Clipper Ship, 7/25/57 (Box 1)
  - Kiley, Richard - CBS, United States Steel Hour: Hidden River, 6/19/58 (Box 1)
  - Kilgallen, Dorothy - CBS, What's My Line, 8/21/57 (Box 2)
  - King, Alice - NBC, Club Oasis, 7/18/58 (Box 1)
  - King, Louise - NBC, Club Oasis, 7/18/58 (Box 1)
  - King, Marilyn - NBC, Club Oasis, 7/18/58 (Box 1)
  - King, Peggy - NBC, Hallmark Hall of Fame: Hans Brinker or The Silver Skates, 1/10/58 (Box 2)
  - King, Yvonne - NBC, Club Oasis, 7/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Kirby, Durward - CBS, Garry Moore Show, 8/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Kirby Stone Four, - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Kirk, Phyllis - NBC, Destiny, 7/15/57 (Box 2)
  - Kirk, Phyllis - NBC, Thin Man (also shown with dog Asta), 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Kirsten, Dorothy - NBC, Chevy Show, 5/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Knotts, Don - NBC, Steve Allen Show, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Kohler, Dennis - CBS, Show of the Month: Member of the Wedding, 5/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Korper, Rene - CBS, Playhouse 90: Homeward Borne, 8/8/57 (Box 1)
  - Kovacs, Ernie - CBS, What's My Line, 8/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Kramer, Jack - CBS, World's Championship Tennis Matches (from Forest Hill, NY), 6/27/57 (Box 2)
  - Krieger, Gloria - CBS, Phil Silvers on Broadway, 5/2/58 (Box 1)
  - Lake, Arthur - NBC, Blondie (shown with dog, Daisy), 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Lamas, Fernando - CBS, Lucille Ball-Desi Arnaz Show, 3/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Landon, Michael - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Hands of the Enemy, 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Landy, John - NBC, Big Moment, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Langdon, Sue Ane - NBC, Steve Allen Show, 5/9/58 (Box 1)
  - Lange, Hope - CBS, Playhouse 90: Innocent Sleep, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - Larkin, John - CBS, Edge of the Night, 4/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Laskov, Chaim, Maj. Gen. - NBC, NBC News: Outlook, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Laughton, Charles - CBS, General Electric Theater: Mister Kensington's Finest Hour, 6/27/58 (Box 1)
  - Laurence, Paula - NBC, Hansel and Gretel (also on radio), 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Lawford, Peter - NBC, Thin Man (also shown with dog Asta), 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Lawrence, Steve - NBC, Steve Allen Show, 1/17/58 (Box 2)
  - Lawrence, Steve - NBC, Steve Allen Presents Steve Lawrence and Eydie Gorme, 6/20/58 (Box 1)
  - Lawrence, Steve - NBC, Steve Allen Presents Steve Lawrence and Eydie Gorme, 8/8/58 (Box 1)
  - Layne, Joy - CBS, Vic Damone Show, 7/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Lazer, Peter - NBC, Affairs of Dr. Gentry (radio broadcast), 5/16/58 (Box 1)
  - Lazer, Peter - NBC, Today is Ours, 6/6/58 (Box 1)
  - Lazer, Peter - NBC, Today is Ours, 8/1/58 (Box 1)
  - Le Gallienne, Eva - CBS, Playhouse 90: Bitter Heritage, 7/22/58 (Box 1)
  - Lear, Joyce - NBC, Today is Ours, 6/6/58 (Box 1)
  - Lee, Billy - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale (Box 2)
  - Lee, Pinky - NBC, Gumby Show (shown with Gumby), 6/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Leigh, Janet - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Carriage from Britain, 8/23/57 (Box 1)
  - Leleku-Papas, Irene - CBS, Climax!: Disappearance of Daphne (Box 1)
  - Lembeck, Harvey - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Gold Fever, 9/5/58 (Box 1)
  - Lemmon, Jack - NBC, Alcoa-Goodyear Anthology, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Leonard, Sheldon - CBS, Danny Thomas Show, 2/7/58 (Box 2)
  - Leonetti, Tommy - NBC, Your Hit Parade, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Lescoulie, Jack - NBC, Today (shown with Kokomo Jr. a chimp) (Box 1)
  - Levene, Sam - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: Mother Bit, 5/31/57 (Box 2)
  - Levenson, Conrad - CBS, Two for the Money, 6/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Levenson, Emily Sue - CBS, Two for the Money, 6/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Levenson, Esther - CBS, Two for the Money, 6/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Levenson, Sam - CBS, Two for the Money, 6/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Lewis, Barton - NBC, Julius La Rosa Show, 7/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Lewis, Mario - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Lewis, Mario - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Lewis, Mario - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - [Frank] Libuse Company, - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Linkletter, Art - NBC, People Are Funny, 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Linkletter, Jack - NBC, Haggis Baggis, 6/20/58 (Box 1)
  - Linkletter, Jack - NBC, Haggis Baggis (shown with 7 other hosts), 7/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Livingston, Mary - CBS, Jack Benny Program, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Lockhart, June - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: Matter of Guilt, A, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - Lockhart, June - CBS, Playhouse 90: Confession, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - Lockhart, June - CBS, Gunsmoke, 2/6/58 (Box 2)
  - Lockhart, June - NBC, Decision: Fear Has Many Faces, 8/8/58 (Box 1)
  - Lockhart, June - CBS, Lassie, 8/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Loden, Barbara - NBC, Today is Ours, 8/8/58 (Box 1)
  - Logan, Ella - CBS, Big Record, 8/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Lollobrigida, Gina - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show, 1/29/58 (Box 2)
  - London, Julie - CBS, Playhouse 90: Without Incident, 8/15/57 (Box 1)
  - Lor, Denise - CBS, Garry Moore Show, 8/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Lord, Majorie - CBS, Danny Thomas Show, 4/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Lord, Marjorie - CBS, Danny Thomas Show, 4/24/58 (Box 1)
  - Lorne, Marion - NBC, Sally, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Love, Phyllis - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Rumpelstiltskin, 1/17/58 (Box 2)
  - Love, Phyllis - NBC, Suspicion: Protegee, 4/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Lovejoy, Frank - CBS, Playhouse 90: Country Husband, 6/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Lovejoy, Frank - NBC, Meet McGraw: Ballerina, 7/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Lovejoy, Frank - NBC, Adventures of McGraw (shown with wife, son Steve and daughter Judy), 3/7/58 (Box 1)
  - Lowe, Jim - CBS, Sing Along, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - Loy, Myrna - CBS, No Second Helping, 6/13/58 (Box 1)
  - Lu, Lisa - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Lu, Lisa - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Lu, Lisa - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale (entire set is shown - with extras) (Box 2)
  - Luna, Barbara - CBS, Have Gun, Will Travel, 5/8/58 (Box 1)
  - Lundigan, William - CBS, Playhouse 90: No Time At All, 1/31/58 (Box 2)
  - Lupino, Ida - CBS, Mr. Adams And Eve, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Lupino, Ida - CBS, Mr. Adams and Eve, 1/30/58 (Box 2)
  - Lynn, Judy - CBS, Big Payoff, 6/13/57 (Box 2)
  - Lynn, Lorna - NBC, Monitor (radio broadcast), 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - MacGregor, Ken - NBC, My True Story (radio broadcast), 6/6/58 (Box 1)
  - Mack, Ted - NBC, Ted Mack's Original Amateur Hour, 8/9/57 (Box 2)
  - Mackay, Dana - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Carriage from Britain, 8/23/57 (Box 1)
  - MacKenzie, Gisele - NBC, Gisele MacKenzie Show (photograph of a painted portrait), 1/10/58 (Box 2)
  - MacManus, Ginger - NBC, Kitty Foyle, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - MacRae, Gordon - NBC, Lux Video Theatre, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Madison, Guy - NBC, Opening Night: Sometimes It Happens, 6/27/58 (Box 1)
  - Malone, Ted - ABC, Colby College Fund Drive (shown with Colby College Glee Club) (Box 1)
  - Manners, Marlene - NBC, Twenty One (shown with 7 other women), 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - March, Candy - CBS, $64,000 Question, 7/1/57 (Box 2)
  - March, Hal - CBS, $64,000 Question, 7/1/57 (Box 2)
  - March, Hal - CBS, $64,000 Question, 7/26/57 (Box 1)
  - March, Hal - NBC, What's It For?, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - March, Peter - CBS, $64,000 Question, 7/1/57 (Box 2)
  - Marchand, Nancy - NBC, Material Witness (Box 1)
  - Marlowe, Bill - WBZ/WBZ, Live Five (Box 1)
  - Marshall, E.G. - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Rip Van Winkle, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Marshall, E.G. - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Rip Van Winkle, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Marshall, E.G. - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Rip Van Winkle (with the skittle bowling dwarfs) (Box 1)
  - Marshall, Herbert - CBS, Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Othello, 6/13/58 (Box 1)
  - Marshall, Joan - CBS, Have Gun, Will Travel, 1/30/58 (Box 2)
  - Martel, Donna - CBS, Lineup: Pawn Ticket Case, 1/22/58 (Box 2)
  - Martin, Andra - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Code of Honor (Box 1)
  - Martin, Andra - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Code of Honor (Box 1)
  - Martin, Dean - CBS, Person to Person (shown with his family), 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Martin, Dean - NBC, Pardners (Box 1)
  - Martin, Eugene - NBC, Jefferson Drum, 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Marvin, Lee - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Easy-Going Man, 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Marvin, Lee - NBC, Manhunt (shown with woman), 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Marvin, Lee - NBC, M Squad: Dolly's Bar, 1/17/58 (Box 2)
  - Marvin, Lee - NBC, M Squad, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - Marx, Groucho - NBC, Best of Groucho, 7/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Marx, Harpo - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Red Mill, 4/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Mason, James - CBS, Playhouse 90: Thundering Wave, 6/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Mathers, Jerry - CBS, Leave It To Beaver, 5/27/58 (Box 1)
  - Mathison, Murray - CBS, Alfred Hitchcock Presents, 5/29/58 (Box 1)
  - May, Elaine - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Red Mill, 4/3/58 (Box 1)
  - May, Elaine - CBS, Keep Talking, 6/30/58 (Box 1)
  - Mayo, Jacqueline - CBS, Millionaire: Story of Wally Bannister, 4/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Mayo, Jacqueline - CBS, Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Othello, 6/13/58 (Box 1)
  - McCarthy, Kevin - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Hands of the Enemy, 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - McCarthy, Kevin - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Hands of the Enemy, 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - McCarthy, Lin - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: Matter of Guilt, A, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - McCormack, Parker - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: Love Me to Pieces, 7/8/57 (Box 2)
  - McGrath, Frank - NBC, Wagon Train: Major Adams Story, 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - McKay, Jim - CBS, Verdict is Yours, 6/17/58 (Box 1)
  - McKnight, Marion - CBS, Miss America Pageant, 8/15/57 (Box 2)
  - McLaglen, Andrew V. - CBS, Have Gun, Will Travel, 2/7/58 (Box 2)
  - McLaglen, Victor - CBS, Have Gun, Will Travel, 2/7/58 (Box 2)
  - McNally, Stephan - CBS, Climax!: House of Doubt (Box 1)
  - McNeil, Claudia - CBS, Show of the Month: Member of the Wedding, 5/29/58 (Box 1)
  - McQueen, Steve - CBS, Wanted: Dead or Alive, 8/21/58 (Box 1)
  - Meade, Julia - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show, 6/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Meade, Julia - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show, 6/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Meeker, Ralph - CBS, Playhouse 90: Four Women in Black, 7/23/57 (Box 2)
  - Meeker, Ralph - NBC, Wagon Train: Man Called Horse, A, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Melvin, Allan - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Gold Fever, 9/5/58 (Box 1)
  - Mercer, Johnny - CBS, Those Whiting Girls, 7/16/57 (Box 2)
  - Meredith, Judy - CBS, George Burns and Gracie Allen Show, 1/31/58 (Box 2)
  - Merill, Dina - CBS, Climax!: Spider Web (Box 1)
  - Middleton, Robert - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Dead Are Silent, 7/19/57 (Box 2)
  - Middleton, Robert - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse, 8/1/58 (Box 1)
  - Milan, Lita - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Contest of Ladies, A, 3/26/58 (Box 1)
  - Milland, Ray - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Girl in the Grass, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - Milland, Ray - NBC, Destiny, 7/15/57 (Box 2)
  - Milland, Ray - NBC, Suspicion: Eye for Eye, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - Miller, Dean - CBS, December Bride, 1/16/58 (Box 2)
  - Milner, Martin - NBC, Wagon Train: Sally Porter Story, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Mineo, Sal - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Aladdin, 2/3/58 (Box 2)
  - Mitchell, James - CBS, Seven Lively Arts: Gold Rush, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Mitchell, Thomas - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Mitchell, Thomas - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale (entire set is shown - with extras) (Box 2)
  - Mitchell, Thomas - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale (Box 2)
  - Moll, Elick - CBS, Playhouse 90: Fabulous Irishman, 6/13/57 (Box 2)
  - Montgomery, George - NBC, Life of Riley: Movie Struck, 1/3/58 (Box 2)
  - Montgomery, George - CBS, General Electric Theater: Thousand Dollar Gun, 7/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Montoya, Carlos - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: Guitar, 8/16/57 (Box 2)
  - Moore, Garry - CBS, Garry Moore Show, 8/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Moore, Garry - CBS, I've Got a Secret, 1/14/58 (Box 2)
  - Moore, Garry - CBS, Timex All-Star Jazz Show, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Moore, Mary Alice - NBC, From These Roots, 6/13/58 (Box 1)
  - Moorehead, Agnes - NBC, Suspicion: Protegee, 4/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Moorehead, Agnes - CBS, Playhouse 90: Dungeon, 4/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Morgan, Harry - CBS, December Bride, 2/6/58 (Box 2)
  - Morgan, Jaye P. - CBS, Timex All-Star Jazz Show, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Morgan, Mac - NBC, Cosi Fan Tutte, 3/7/58 (Box 1)
  - Morris, Carolyn - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet (Box 2)
  - Morrow, Vic - CBS, Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Little Sleep, 6/3/57 (Box 2)
  - Muni, Paul - CBS, Playhouse 90: Last Clear Chance, 8/26/58 (Box 1)
  - Murray, Jan - NBC, Treasure Hunt (Box 1)
  - Murray, Jan - NBC, Dollar a Second (shown with his wife), 6/7/57 (Box 2)
  - Murray, Jan - NBC, Treasure Hunt (shown with 7 other hosts), 7/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Murray, Jan - NBC, Treasure Hunt (shown with 2 contestants) (Box 1)
  - Murray, Janice - NBC, Treasure Hunt, 7/12/57 (Box 2)
  - Murray, Kathleen - NBC, Kitty Foyle, 1/17/58 (Box 2)
  - Murray, Kathleen - NBC, Kitty Foyle, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Murray, Kathryn - NBC, Arthur Murray Party, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Murrow, Edward R. - CBS, See It Now: Automation: Weal or Woe, 5/31/57 (Box 2)
  - Murrow, Edward R. - CBS, See It Now: From Precinct To President, 1/20/58 (Box 2)
  - Mussolini, - CBS, Twentieth Century (Mussolini's Son) (Box 2)
  - Myerson, Bess - CBS, Miss America Pageant, 8/15/57 (Box 2)
  - Myerson, Bess - CBS, Big Payoff, 2/3/58 (Box 2)
  - Narz, Jack - CBS, Dotto, 4/10/58 (Box 1)
  - Narz, Jack - NBC, Dotto, 5/27/58 (Box 1)
  - Narz, Jack - NBC, Dotto (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Barry - CBS, My Favorite Husband, 6/12/57 (Box 2)
  - Nelson, Dave - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie an Harriet: Fixing Up the Fraternity House (Box 1)
  - Nelson, David - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet. The: Code of Honor (Box 1)
  - Nelson, David - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Tutti Frutti Ice Cream (Box 1)
  - Nelson, David - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet (Box 2)
  - Nelson, David - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet (Box 2)
  - Nelson, David - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Code of Honor (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Harriet - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Harriet - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Top Gun (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Harriet - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Reading Room (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Harriet - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Bachelor (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Harriet - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Harriet's Dancing Partner (Box 2)
  - Nelson, Harriet - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet (Box 2)
  - Nelson, Lindsey - NBC, Major League Baseball, 3/7/58 (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Ozzie - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Cruise for Harriet, A (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Ozzie - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Magic of Three (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Ozzie - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Rick's Chemistry Grade (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Ozzie - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Ozzie - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Top Gun (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Ozzie - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Reading Room (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Ozzie - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Bachelor (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Ozzie - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Record Trout (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Ozzie - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Dave and the Men's Club (Box 2)
  - Nelson, Ozzie - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Safe (Box 2)
  - Nelson, Ozzie - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Harriet's Dancing Partner (Box 2)
  - Nelson, Ozzie - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet (Box 2)
  - Nelson, Rick - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Ricky is Micky (Box 1)
  - Nelson, Rick - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet (Box 2)
  - Nelson, Ricky - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet (Box 2)
  - Nettleton, Lois - CBS, United States Steel Hour: Hidden River, 6/19/58 (Box 1)
  - Nichols, Barbara - CBS, Red Skelton Show, 5/22/58 (Box 1)
  - Nichols, Mike - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Red Mill, 4/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Nichols, Mike - CBS, Keep Talking, 6/30/58 (Box 1)
  - Nimmo, Bill - CBS, For Love or Money, 6/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Nimmo, Bill - CBS, For Love or Money, 7/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Niven, David - NBC, Alcoa-Goodyear Anthology, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Nolan, Lloyd - CBS, Playhouse 90: Galvanized Yankee, 6/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Nolan, Tommy - NBC, Buckskin, 6/20/58 (Box 1)
  - Norton, Cliff - CBS, United States Steel Hour: Side Show, 6/24/57 (Box 2)
  - Norton, Cliff - CBS, Studio One Summer Theatre: Love Me to Pieces, 7/8/57 (Box 2)
  - Nye, Louis - NBC, Steve Allen Show, 6/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Nye, Louis - NBC, Steve Allen Show, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Oberon, Merle - NBC, Destiny, 7/15/57 (Box 2)
  - O'Brien, Edmond - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse, 8/1/58 (Box 1)
  - O'Brien, Karin - NBC, Price is Right (shown with 3 other contestants) (Box 1)
  - O'Brien, Kerin - NBC, Price is Right, 2/6/58 (Box 2)